Hi.
Hey!
Oh, my God!
Welcome back.
How was the honeymoon?
Oh, incredible.
Oh, champagne,
candlelit dinners,
moonlight walks on the beach.
It was so romantic.
So where's Mike?
Oh, he's at the doctor.
He didn't poop
the whole time we were there.
Well, anyway,
I'm glad you're back.
I really need your help.
Oh, why? What's up?
Well, I have an audition
for this play,
and for some of it,
I have to speak French.
Which, according to my resume,
I'm fluent in.
Joey, you shouldn't lie
on your resume.
Yeah, you really shouldn't.
By the way, how was that
yearlong dig in Cairo?
( softly ):
It was okay.
I did not know
you spoke French.
Oui, bien sur
je parle francais.
( continues speaking French )
Oh. You're so sexy.
JOEY:
So will you help me?
I really want to be
in this play.
Sure.
( speaking French )
Seriously, stop it
or I'm gonna jump on you.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey.
Why are you wearing
my apron?
I'm making cookies for Erica.
By the way, we have to leave
for the airport soon.
Her plane comes in
in about an hour.
Oh, hey, when she gets here, is
it okay if I introduce you two
as my wife, and the woman
who's carrying my child?
No?
Divorce?
Hey.
You guys know where Rachel is?
I haven't seen her
since this morning.
It's unbelievable.
She was supposed to meet me
a half hour ago with Emma.
Hey.
Hey!
These are for Erica.
What, she's going to eat
all those cookies?
Well, I want the baby to
come out all cute and fat.
So why is Erica coming to visit?
Because we want to get
to know her better, and, uh...
Plus, she's never been
to New York,
so she's wants to see
all the tourist spots:
the Statue of Liberty
and Empire State Building...
Those places,
there's always so many people,
and they're being corralled
like cattle.
And there's always
some idiot who goes "moo."
Well, if it annoys you so much,
then why do you do it?
Oh, hi. Hi.
Thanks for showing up
30 minutes late.
Ross...
No, no, no, I'm sure
you have a great excuse.
What was it,
a hair appointment?
A mani-pedi?
Was there a sale at Barney's?
My father had a heart attack...
while I was at Barney's.
Oh, my God.
Honey...
I'm so sorry.
Is he okay?
Yeah, they said
he's going to be fine,
but he's still
heavily sedated.
Okay, okay, I'm going
to come out
to Long Island with you.
I mean, you can't be alone
right now.
No, come on,
I'm totally okay.
( cries ):
I don't need you to come.
I can totally
handle this on my own.
Still, still, let me
come... for me.
Okay, if you
really need to.
I bet someone could use
one of Monica's
freshly baked cookies.
( gasps ):
Oh, I really could.
All right, this seems
pretty simple.
Your first line is,
"My name is Claude."
So just repeat after me.
Je m'appelle Claude.
Je de coup, plau.
Well, let's just...
let's try it again.
Okay.
Je m'appelle Claude.
Je de ple, mloo.
Huh.
It's not quite
what I'm saying.
Really?
Sounds exactly
the same to me.
It does, really?
Yeah.
All right, let's just
try it again.
Really listen.
Got it.
( slowly ):
Okay. Je m'appelle Claude.
Je da flup, flee.
Oh, mon dieu.
Oh, de foof.
Hey, you guys.
Hi.
Hey.
I want you to meet
someone really special.
Phoebe, this is Erica.
And this is the baby.
Joey... Erica. Baby.
Hi.
Everyone...
Erica. Baby.
Monica. Calm. Self.
JOEY:
Hey, sit down.
There you go.
Thank you.
It's really nice
to meet you guys.
I can't believe
I'm here.
Welcome to New York City.
Or should I say...
Gue de floof,
New York City.
Why would you
say that?
Okay, what are you going
to be doing today?
Well, I want to see everything:
Times Square, Coney Island,
Rockefeller Center.
Oh, you know what you should do?
You should walk all
the way to the top
of the Statue of Liberty.
Oh, yeah, let's do that.
Great.
This baby better be really good.
Hi. Excuse me, I'm here
to see my father.
My name is Rachel Green.
And I'm Dr. Ross Geller.
Ross,
please, this is
a hospital, okay.
That actually means
something here.
So can we please go in?
Absolutely.
Rach, I think I'm gonna
wait out here because, uh...
my throat is feeling
a little scratchy.
I don't want to infect him.
Ross, please, don't be
so scared of him.
I'm not scared of him,
I'm really sick.
He's under sedation,
so he's pretty much out.
I'm feeling better.
( gasps )
Oh, my God.
Oh. Oh, wow,
that ear and nose
hair trimmer I got him
was just money
down the drain, huh?
Ms. Green, your father's doctor
is on the phone
if you'd like to speak to him.
Oh, great.
Are you going to be okay?
He's unconscious.
I think we'll be just fine.
Okay.
( horses neigh, dinosaur roars)
( roars )
( chuckles )
Um, did... did the TV wake you?
No.
When you put your feet up
on my bed,
you tugged on my catheter.
Ouchie.
What are you doing here, Geller?
I came with Rachel,
who should be back any second.
So what's new?
Oh, I had a little heart attack.
Right. Is it painful?
What, the heart attack,
or sitting here talking to you?
( chuckles nervously )
Let's see if we can get
that Rachel back here.
So what's new
with you?
Knocked up any more
of my daughters lately?
Nope. Just the one.
Rach!
Je m'appelle Claude.
Je dup kol, mlu.
No!
Okay.
Maybe if we just break it down.
Okay, let's just... let's try it
one syllable at a time.
Okay, so repeat after me.
Je.
M'a.
Pelle.
Great.
Okay, faster.
Je.
M'a.
Pelle.
Je m'appelle.
Me poo poo.
Okay, it's too hard.
I can't teach you.
What are you doing?
I have to go before
I put your head through a wall.
No, no! Don't go.
I need you.
My audition is tomorrow.
Ja blu bla!
Me la pee!
Oom blah!
Poo.
Hey.
Hi.
I was going to make us
some dinner,
but all I found in
your dad's fridge
was bacon and heavy cream.
I think we solved the mystery
of the heart attack.
Did you call your parents?
Oh, yeah.
Emma's doing great.
Oh, good.
Wow.
What?
Just can't believe
I'm in Rachel Green's room.
What do you mean?
You've been in my room before.
Yeah, sure, right.
Like I'd ever be
in Rachel Green's room.
Okay, I gotta tell you,
it's really weird
when you use my whole name.
Sorry.
You okay?
Yeah.
You had a rough day, huh?
Just so weird seeing him
like that, you know?
I mean, he's a doctor.
You don't expect
doctors to get sick.
But we do.
You know,
he's going to be okay, Rach.
Oh, I don't want him
to wake up alone.
I should go to the hospital.
No, no.
Hey, hey, hey, look.
What?
They gave him a
lot of medication, okay?
He wouldn't even know
if you were there.
We'll go see him first
thing in the morning, okay?
Really?
I shouldn't feel guilty?
No. Hey, Rach, you've been
an amazing daughter, okay?
Right now you just need
to get some rest.
Okay, maybe you're right.
Good night.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Would you stay here with me
for a little while?
Sure.
Okay.
Thank you for coming
with me today.
Oh, of course.
Rachel Green is very
happy you're in her room.
Me, too.
Come here.
I just don't want
to be alone tonight.
Okay, well, um...
I can maybe grab
a sleeping bag or...
Oh...
Oh.
No, Rach!
I'm sorry, I just...
I just don't think this...
this is a good idea.
Well, we won't know that
until we do it, will we?
Uh, look, um, you are upset
about your father
and you're feeling vulnerable.
And I just don't feel
it would be right.
I feel like I'd be, you know,
taking advantage of you.
Taking advantage?
I'm giving you the advantage.
Enjoy.
Look, I'm sure
it would be great.
But I think one of us
has to be thinking clearly.
So I'm going to go.
Wow. Okay.
I'll see you
in the morning.
Mm-hmm.
Haven't had sex in four months.
I should get a medal for that.
Thanks so much for taking me
to all those places.
I had a great time.
Oh, I'm glad.
Listen, I want to apologize
about Chandler, though.
I just did not
see this coming.
New York is awesome!
What is with you?
You know, I've been
to these places before,
but I've never really seen them,
you know?
Yeah, you miss a lot
when you're mooing.
Thanks so much
for showing me around.
Oh, it was our pleasure.
We're so much enjoying
getting to know you.
Well, if there's anything else
you want to know...
Oh. Uh...
okay.
Um, do you mind if we ask you
some questions about the father?
Oh, sure. Yeah.
He was my high school
boyfriend.
Captain of the football team.
Really cute.
And he got a scholarship
and went off to college.
That's great.
Yeah, it's almost
definitely him.
How's that now?
Well, there's a chance
it's another guy.
I mean, I've only ever
been with two guys,
but they sort of overlapped.
So what does
the other guy do?
Does he go to college, too?
No, he's in prison.
Oh. Was he falsely
accused of something?
No, he killed his father
with a shovel.
But other than that,
he's a great guy.
I'll bet his dad
doesn't think so.
Are you awake?
Of course I'm awake!
Assume from now on
that I'm always awake!
All right.
We don't know
that it's him.
I mean, it could be
the football guy.
Honey, it's us!
Of course
it's the shovel killer!
All right, let's say
that it is him.
Would we not want the baby? No.
Would you treat
him any differently?
I'd keep an eye on him!
We have to find out
which one the father is.
How?
I don't know.
They have tests
for these things, right?
Yeah, but maybe
we're just overreacting.
Easy for you to say.
He's a father killer.
He probably loves
his mommy.
He's probably got a tattoo
then says "Mom"
on his shovel-wielding arm.
MAN:
We'll now count
from one to five.
Un, deux, trois, quatre, cinq.
Enh, bluh, blah, fluh, flank.
Good job.
Thank you.
Hey.
Hey, Joey.
Listen, I feel really
badly about yesterday.
And I thought about it a lot.
I was too impatient.
So let's try it again.
No, that's okay.
I don't need your help.
I worked on it myself.
And I gotta say
I am pretty good.
Really? Can I hear
some of it?
Sure, sure.
Okay.
( clears throat )
Blay de la blay
de blu blah blay!
See?
You're not...
Again, you're not
speaking French!
Oh, well, I think I am!
Yeah. And I think I'm definitely
going to get the part.
How could you
possibly think that?
For one thing,
the guy on the tape
said I was doing a good job!
Hey, Rach, could you
grab me a cup of coffee?
Sure.
You've been quiet
all morning.
Is everything okay?
Mm-hmm.
You sure
you're all right?
Yep.
Okay.
Um, well, I'm going to go
grab us some breakfast.
FYI...
There it is.
In the future,
when a girl asks for some
ill-advised sympathy sex,
just do it.
Wait, wait.
You're mad at me
about last night?
I was just trying
to do the right thing.
Really?
Well, it seems to me
if you'd done the right thing,
I would not have woken
up today
feeling stupid
and embarrassed.
I would have woken up
feeling comforted and satisfied.
Well...
Oh, stop that!
I can't believe this.
What do you... I...
I was just being a good guy.
I treated you
with respect and understanding.
Oh, that's so hot.
Hey, I was looking out
for you!
Oh, really?
Well, Ross,
you know what?
I am a big girl.
I don't need someone
telling me
what is best for me.
I got to say
I've not had sex
a lot of times before.
This is the worst ever.
Oh, really? Really?
Well, it wasn't very good
for me, either.
Oh, okay.
Hey, hey, you know what?
You know what?
To avoid this
little thing
in the future,
let's just say--
you and me?
Never having sex again.
What?
That's right.
Sex is off the table.
I am never having sex
with you again.
Dr. Green,
are you feeling better?
Hey.
How was lunch?
We had a good time.
By the way, I wanted
to ask you something.
It would really mean
a lot to me--
if the baby was a boy--
that you name him
after my father,
Jiminy Billy Bob.
Oh, really?
No!
You were right.
That was fun.
I'm going to go finish packing.
Okay.
So, is she going
to take the test?
Nope. She doesn't have to.
I found out
who the father is.
Oh, God.
It's Shovely Joe,
isn't it?
No, it's not.
How do you know?
Well, it turns out
that Erica didn't
pay much attention
is sex ed class
'cause the thing
she did with that prison guy?
It'd be pretty hard
to make a baby that way.
Oh, God, what was it?
The thing we hardly
ever do,
or the thing
we never do?
The thing we never do.
Shovely Joe.
Whenever you're ready, Joey.
Right.
Jai boo boo, Claude.
Uh, sle poo.
Laylu blah blu.
I'm sorry. What's going on?
Dude, come on.
French it up.
Joey,
do you speak French?
Toot de la smor!
Blu, blu ay, blu blah. Foo...
You know what?
I think this audition is over.
( French accent ):
Excuse me.
I am Regine Filange.
I was passing by
when I heard this man
speaking the, the
regional dialect
of my French town
of Estee Lauder.
You really think
this man is speaking French?
Oh, sa sa!
( speaking French )
( continues speaking French )
Good job, little buddy.
That was some
really good French.
But I think
we're going to go
with someone
else for the part.
Oh. All right.
But my French was good?
It was great.
See?
Merci, au revoir.
Tout de la fruit.
Emma's down for the night.
Oh, good.
So I guess
I'm going to take off.
Okay.
Hey, listen,
just before you go.
Again, I just want to say
thank you for coming with me.
Oh, no problem.
And also, you know,
I, uh, I was thinking
about what you said,
you know,
about the whole sex thing,
and...
probably not a great idea
to go down that road again.
Thank you.
I'm glad, I'm glad you agree.
It's a shame, though.
I mean, when we did it,
it was pretty good.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
Hey, do you remember
that one really great time?
Oh, yeah.
You know,
it was your birthday.
Valentine's Day.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I guess that's all
in the past now.
Mm-hmm.
Not even one more time.
Not even once.
No matter how much
we want it.
Even if we want it
really bad.
That's what we decided.
That's right.
It's kinda hard, though,
Yeah.
you know?
When two people
have a connection, you know
that's... just seems
like such a... waste.
I hate waste.
Ross?
Yes?
Just so you know...
with us...
it's never off the table.
Damn it.
It's never off the table.
Okay, can you
really tap dance?
No.
It's off the resume.
Archery?
Nope.
Horseback riding?
Would fall off a lot.
You can drink a gallon
of milk in ten seconds?
That I can do.
Come on.
You can drink a gallon
of milk in ten seconds?
All right, watch me.
Okay, you time me. Ready?
Ready.
Go!
You did it!
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org